liveabroad.com 2008-12-18

# Privacy Policy

****Liveabroad.com Privacy Policy Statement****

Thank you for visiting our site, [www.liveabroad.com](http://www.liveabroad.com/). We want you to know that we are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Policy Statement is to inform you of the types of information we collect from visitors to our site, how we may use that information and whether we disclose that information to anyone.

**What Information We Collect and How We Use It**  
Information we collect on our site generally falls into the category of Personally Identifiable Information. Personally Identifiable Information means information that lets us know specifically who you are. You can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. 

Registration at our message board -.You may become an associate member or register to use our message board without disclosing Personally Identifiable Information. If you choose to answer the optional questions (those not marked *), this additional information is seen only by the principals of [www.liveabroad.com](http://www.liveabroad.com/). We do not use this information in soliciting orders for products or services, nor do we share it with any third parties.

Financial transactions \- When you place an order for products or services offered at our site, we collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, contact and billing information, credit card and other transaction information). We use this information to process payment, communicate with you about the status of your order and deliver your order. Your delivery information is provided to the carrier, usually the postal department. Credit card information is not retained on our site. 

Cookies - Our message board permits cookies to be stored on your computer to make it easier for you to use the message board. Most browsers can to be set to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Please note that if you choose to erase or block cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to post at the message board. If you choose to change your preferences regarding cookies, you may do so by clicking on Forum Preferences at the message board.

Changes to your information - You may make changes to the information you have given us at our message board by clicking on Profile at the message board.

**Sharing Your Information**   
We do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise transmit any Personally Identifiable Information to any other company or person for any reason. Information you provide us in financial transactions is stored by us in hard copy for one year only.

At our message board, you may make your e-mail address available to others only if you wish to. We will not give out your e-mail address.

**Links To Other Web Sites**   
Links to third-party web sites are provided at our site. When you use these links, you are leaving our site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those web sites linked to our site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies.

**Changes To This Statement**   
Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement will be posted here on our site, and the date of the newest version is posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed.

By using our site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Policy Statement in effect at the time of use.

**Contact Us**   
If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Policy Statement, please e-mail us at [info@liveabroad.com](mailto:info@liveabroad.com). We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.

May 2005.
